bidrivals.com 2012-06-21

# Privacy | Penny Auctions - BidRivals | USA

## General

BidRivals strives to protect the privacy of any personal information provided by our customers. The main aim of this policy is to inform you how we shall collect and make use of such information. Please read the policy stipulated below carefully prior to providing us with any personal information.

Personal Information is the definition used to describe ‘any information collected from you during the registration process’ e.g. name, surname, address, e-mail address, phone number, and your future activity at BidRivals. We will also ask for your payment details, however this information will be held by our third party payment providers as we do not have direct access to your payment details.

## Changing/Updating personal information

You may view, change and update most of your personal information at any time by logging on to your BidRivals account. Due to security reasons, certain personal information may only be changed by means of contacting our customer support team.

## Account Termination

Should you wish to terminate your BidRivals account, you are entitled to do so at any time by contacting our customer support team. Subsequently, all of your personal information will be removed from view whilst access to your account shall be blocked at the earliest.  
BidRivals is obliged by Law to store any personal information from closed accounts, as this information may be used to prevent illegal activities, enforce our Terms and Conditions, resolve any problems or disputes and assist legal authorities with any investigations.

## Use of Personal Information

We make use of your personal information in order to provide you with a fast and efficient service. The information collected is used in order to contact you directly, for payment processing, keeping track of all of your auctions as well as informing you about any new releases or promotional material. By opening an account with BidRivals, you also allow us to use your personal information in order to prevent any potential illegal activities and to enforce our Terms and Conditions.

## Sharing Personal Information

In the event that we are obliged to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements, or to protect our rights or property (including the exchange of information with other companies and organizations for the following purposes: verification, fraud protection and credit risk reduction), your personal information may be disclosed to an applicable governmental, regulatory or enforcement authority.

## Use of cookies

To make your visit on BidRivals as simple and user friendly as possible, BidRivals is collecting information (cookie) submitted by your web browser. This information is used to predetermine the correct site and language of your account, keep track of all your auctions and improve our site and offered promotions. In case you would not like us to collect cookies you may prohibit so by disabling the cookie collection functionality accessible from your browser settings, kindly refer to your individual browser instructions. Please be aware that by switching off cookie collection, this may restrict your full usage of our BidRivals website.

## Security Measures

The personal information which you provide during the registration process is password protected and may only be accessible by yourself. It is your sole and exclusive responsibility to ensure that your login details are kept safe and secure. Please note that you must not disclose your login details to anyone. BidRivals will under no circumstances request your password. BidRivals is not responsible for any abuse or misuse of your account by third parties due to your disclosure, whether intentional or accidental.

## Consent

By registering an account with BidRivals and taking part in our auctions, you accept this privacy policy and you give consent to BidRivals to share your personal information with mentioned parties referred to in this document as stipulated above. If you do not agree with sharing parts of your information with third parties, please contact us immediately or request termination of your BidRivals account.
